elpida.com 2016-04-01

# Micron Technology, Inc. - Privacy

## Micron's Privacy Policy

Micron is committed to protecting your right to privacy when visiting our websites. We recognize that when you share your personal information with us, you expect us to treat that information in a serious and responsible manner. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use that information, and how you can correct or change that information. In summary, you should know that:

  * This Privacy Policy only applies to information gathered from Micron’s publicly available websites. 
  * Micron collects personal information to provide you products and services and to process job applications.
  * Micron has security measures in place to help keep your personal information secure. 
  * Micron will not sell your personal information. The only exception is described in the Change of Control section below.

### Security

Micron's websites have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, including protecting information behind a firewall within a perimeter network and encrypting your ordering information during transmission.

### Information We Collect

If you choose to register with Micron, place an order with us, participate in one of our surveys or contests, apply for a job, or otherwise contact us, we may ask that you provide us with relevant information such as contact information (first and last name, e-mail address and telephone number), financial information (account or credit card numbers), demographic information (address, age, or income level), unique identifiers (tax ID number), information about where you learned of our products, and information about your intended use of our products. We do not purge customer information on a regular basis, so information you provide us will remain in our systems for an indefinite amount of time. We may use your contact information to send you information about us and to contact you when necessary. If you do not want to receive any mailings from us, please see the Choice/Opt-Out section below. Financial information is used to determine your creditworthiness and to charge you for products you order. Demographic information may be used to tailor your experience at our websites, show you information that we think you might be interested in, and present information according to your preferences. In addition, our sales and marketing departments may use demographic information, information about where you learned of our products, and information about your intended use of our products to improve our advertising and marketing efforts and to measure interest in our products.

### Public Forums

Micron may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to you. Because any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, you should exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose your personal information.

### Children's Guidelines

Micron's websites are not generally directed to children. Micron does maintain a few web pages designed to provide young people educational and charitable information, but those web pages do not collect personal information. If you are under 18, do not supply any personal information to any Micron website. If you wish to purchase a product from a Micron website, please ask your parent or guardian to make the purchase for you. 

### IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer and improve our websites, and gather demographic information to measure interest in our websites and products.

### Tracking Technologies: Cookies/Beacons/Do Not Track Signals/Etc.

For information about how this website uses various tracking technologies, visit our Cookie Policy page.

### Supplemental Information

We may supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For example, Micron may use information that we purchase from a database marketing information firm to enhance our understanding of the information that you provide.

### Links to Other Sites

Micron's websites contain links to other sites. Micron is not responsible for the privacy practices, goods and services, or content of such websites.

### Third-Party Suppliers

We employ many other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service.

### Anti-Fraud Checks

We may use personal information provided to us to conduct anti-fraud checks that may help us detect and prevent fraud. The personal information we receive may be disclosed to a credit reference agency, fraud prevention agency or other information provider, which may keep a record of that information.

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about Micron's privacy policy or the privacy practices of our websites, you may use one of the specific choices below or you may contact us by email at [privacy@micron.com](mailto:privacy@micron.com).

  * **Choice/Opt-Out:**
    * Our sites provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any point where we request information. If you do not want to receive future communications from us, please either go back to the website from which you no longer wish to receive such communications or contact us by sending an email to [privacy@micron.com](mailto:privacy@micron.com). 

  * **Correct/Update:  
**
    * If you want to change or modify information you have previously provided to us, please either go back to the website where you provided such information or contact us by sending an email to [privacy@micron.com](mailto:privacy@micron.com). 

### Compliance Hotline

Micron believes in ethical business practices. You may review our Code of Business Conduct and Ethics which can be found in the “Governance” section of the “Our Commitment” webpage (there is a link at the bottom of this webpage). if you have any concerns, please contact us as described above or you may contact our Compliance Hotline.

### U.S. Commerce Department Safe Harbor Principles

Micron complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Micron has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

In compliance with the European and Switzerland Safe Harbor Principles, Micron commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Micron at [privacy@micron.com](mailto:privacy@micron.com). Micron has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the European Union and Switzerland Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Micron, please visit the BBB SAFE HARBOR website at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. 

### Change of Control

If another company acquires assets related to this website, or if we experience some other change of control event such as a spin-off, merger, insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, we reserve the right to include any or all user-related information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company. We cannot guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with any of these transactions will comply with all the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Updates/Effective Date

Micron reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes to this Privacy Policy will apply to information we have received and information we receive after the revised Privacy Policy is effective. When we do amend this Privacy Policy, the revised Policy will be posted here so please visit this Web page to view the most current Privacy Policy. The effective date of this version of the Privacy Policy is May 18, 2015.
